{
    "subject": "resource/The_Legend_of_White_Fang",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Series",
    "human_readable": "The Legend of White Fang is a series.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7379271388053894,
            "question": "What is the setting of 'The Legend of White Fang'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6927739381790161,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the characters in 'The Legend of White Fang'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6854823231697083,
            "question": "Is 'The Legend of White Fang' a single story or multiple stories?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6678981184959412,
            "question": "Is there a particular historical period that 'The Legend of White Fang' is set in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.658798336982727,
            "question": "What type of work is 'The Legend of White Fang'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6344304084777832,
            "question": "What themes are explored in 'The Legend of White Fang'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5633699893951416,
            "question": "Who is the author of 'The Legend of White Fang'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5503063201904297,
            "question": "What kind of animals are featured in 'The Legend of White Fang'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5389360785484314,
            "question": "What makes 'The Legend of White Fang' unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4778788089752197,
            "question": "Has 'The Legend of White Fang' been adapted into other media formats?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Legend of White Fang is a series.",
            "html": "dbpedia_299_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes 'The Legend of White Fang' unique?",
            "html": "dbpedia_299_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of animals are featured in 'The Legend of White Fang'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_299_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the author of 'The Legend of White Fang'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_299_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_299_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_299_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_299_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_299_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_299_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_299_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_299_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_299_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_299_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_299_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, I can evaluate whether the triple \"The Legend of White Fang is a series\" is supported by the documents.\n\nHere's my evaluation:\n\n* In document 23.txt, it is stated that \"The Legend of White Fang is a cartoon series.\" which supports the triple.\n* In documents 43.txt, 21.txt, 55.txt, and 91.txt, it is consistently mentioned that \"The Legend of White Fang is a cartoon series\" or \"an animated television series\", which further supports the triple.\n\nTherefore, my answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references indicating that \"The Legend of White Fang\" is indeed a cartoon or animated series, which aligns with the statement \"The Legend of White Fang is a series.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}